

export const flashcards = [

    { category: "hiragana", front: "あ", back: "a" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "い", back: "i" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "う", back: "u" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "え", back: "e" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "お", back: "o" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "か", back: "ka" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "き", back: "ki" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "く", back: "ku" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "け", back: "ke" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "こ", back: "ko" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "さ", back: "sa" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "し", back: "shi" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "す", back: "su" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "せ", back: "se" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "そ", back: "so" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "た", back: "ta" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "ち", back: "chi" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "つ", back: "tsu" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "て", back: "te" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "と", back: "to" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "な", back: "na" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "に", back: "ni" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "ぬ", back: "nu" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "ね", back: "ne" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "の", back: "no" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "は", back: "ha" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "ひ", back: "hi" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "ふ", back: "fu" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "へ", back: "he" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "ほ", back: "ho" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "ま", back: "ma" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "み", back: "mi" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "む", back: "mu" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "め", back: "me" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "も", back: "mo" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "や", back: "ya" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "ゆ", back: "yu" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "よ", back: "yo" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "ら", back: "ra" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "り", back: "ri" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "る", back: "ru" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "れ", back: "re" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "ろ", back: "ro" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "わ", back: "wa" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "を", back: "wo" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "ん", back: "n" },

    { category: "hiragana", front: "が", back: "ga" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "ぎ", back: "gi" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "ぐ", back: "gu" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "げ", back: "ge" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "ご", back: "go" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "ざ", back: "za" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "じ", back: "ji" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "ず", back: "zu" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "ぜ", back: "ze" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "ぞ", back: "zo" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "だ", back: "da" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "ぢ", back: "ji" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "づ", back: "zu" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "で", back: "de" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "ど", back: "do" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "ば", back: "ba" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "び", back: "bi" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "ぶ", back: "bu" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "べ", back: "be" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "ぼ", back: "bo" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "ぱ", back: "pa" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "ぴ", back: "pi" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "ぷ", back: "pu" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "ぺ", back: "pe" },
    { category: "hiragana", front: "ぽ", back: "po" },

    { category: "katakana", front: "ア", back: "a" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "イ", back: "i" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "ウ", back: "u" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "エ", back: "e" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "オ", back: "o" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "カ", back: "ka" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "キ", back: "ki" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "ク", back: "ku" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "ケ", back: "ke" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "コ", back: "ko" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "サ", back: "sa" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "シ", back: "shi" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "ス", back: "su" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "セ", back: "se" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "ソ", back: "so" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "タ", back: "ta" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "チ", back: "chi" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "ツ", back: "tsu" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "テ", back: "te" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "ト", back: "to" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "ナ", back: "na" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "ニ", back: "ni" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "ヌ", back: "nu" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "ネ", back: "ne" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "ノ", back: "no" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "ハ", back: "ha" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "ヒ", back: "hi" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "フ", back: "fu" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "ヘ", back: "he" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "ホ", back: "ho" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "マ", back: "ma" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "ミ", back: "mi" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "ム", back: "mu" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "メ", back: "me" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "モ", back: "mo" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "ヤ", back: "ya" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "ユ", back: "yu" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "ヨ", back: "yo" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "ラ", back: "ra" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "リ", back: "ri" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "ル", back: "ru" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "レ", back: "re" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "ロ", back: "ro" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "ワ", back: "wa" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "ヲ", back: "wo" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "ン", back: "n" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "ガ", back: "ga" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "ギ", back: "gi" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "グ", back: "gu" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "ゲ", back: "ge" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "ゴ", back: "go" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "ザ", back: "za" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "ジ", back: "ji" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "ズ", back: "zu" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "ゼ", back: "ze" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "ゾ", back: "zo" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "ダ", back: "da" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "ヂ", back: "ji" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "ヅ", back: "zu" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "デ", back: "de" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "ド", back: "do" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "バ", back: "ba" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "ビ", back: "bi" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "ブ", back: "bu" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "ベ", back: "be" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "ボ", back: "bo" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "パ", back: "pa" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "ピ", back: "pi" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "プ", back: "pu" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "ペ", back: "pe" },
    { category: "katakana", front: "ポ", back: "po" },

   
    { category: "math", front: "2 x 1", back: "2" },
    { category: "math", front: "2 x 2", back: "4" },
    { category: "math", front: "2 x 3", back: "6" },
    { category: "math", front: "2 x 4", back: "8" },
    { category: "math", front: "2 x 5", back: "10" },
    { category: "math", front: "2 x 6", back: "12" },
    { category: "math", front: "2 x 7", back: "14" },
    { category: "math", front: "2 x 8", back: "16" },
    { category: "math", front: "2 x 9", back: "18" },
    { category: "math", front: "2 x 10", back: "20" },
    { category: "math", front: "2 x 11", back: "22" },
    { category: "math", front: "2 x 12", back: "24" },

    { category: "math", front: "3 x 1", back: "3" },
    { category: "math", front: "3 x 2", back: "6" },
    { category: "math", front: "3 x 3", back: "9" },
    { category: "math", front: "3 x 4", back: "12" },
    { category: "math", front: "3 x 5", back: "15" },
    { category: "math", front: "3 x 6", back: "18" },
    { category: "math", front: "3 x 7", back: "21" },
    { category: "math", front: "3 x 8", back: "24" },
    { category: "math", front: "3 x 9", back: "27" },
    { category: "math", front: "3 x 10", back: "30" },
    { category: "math", "front": "3 x 11", "back": "33" },
    { category: "math", "front": "3 x 12", "back": "36" },
   
    { category: "math", "front": "4 x 1", "back": "4" },
    { category: "math", "front": "4 x 2", "back": "8" },
    { category: "math", "front": "4 x 3", "back": "12" },
    { category: "math", "front": "4 x 4", "back": "16" },
    { category: "math", "front": "4 x 5", "back": "20" },
    { category: "math", "front": "4 x 6", "back": "24" },
    { category: "math", "front": "4 x 7", "back": "28" },
    { category: "math", "front": "4 x 8", "back": "32" },
    { category: "math", "front": "4 x 9", "back": "36" },
    { category: "math", "front": "4 x 10", "back": "40" },
    { category: "math", "front": "4 x 11", "back": "44" },
    { category: "math", "front": "4 x 12", "back": "48" },
   
    { category: "math", "front": "5 x 1", "back": "5" },
    { category: "math", "front": "5 x 2", "back": "10" },
    { category: "math", "front": "5 x 3", "back": "15" },
    { category: "math", "front": "5 x 4", "back": "20" },
    { category: "math", "front": "5 x 5", "back": "25" },
    { category: "math", "front": "5 x 6", "back": "30" },
    { category: "math", "front": "5 x 7", "back": "35" },
    { category: "math", "front": "5 x 8", "back": "40" },
    { category: "math", "front": "5 x 9", "back": "45" },
    { category: "math", "front": "5 x 10", "back": "50" },
    { category: "math", "front": "5 x 11", "back": "55" },
    { category: "math", "front": "5 x 12", "back": "60" },
    
    { category: "math", "front": "6 x 1", "back": "6" },
    { category: "math", "front": "6 x 2", "back": "12" },
    { category: "math", "front": "6 x 3", "back": "18" },
    { category: "math", "front": "6 x 4", "back": "24" },
    { category: "math", "front": "6 x 5", "back": "30" },
    { category: "math", "front": "6 x 6", "back": "36" },
    { category: "math", "front": "6 x 7", "back": "42" },
    { category: "math", "front": "6 x 8", "back": "48" },
    { category: "math", "front": "6 x 9", "back": "54" },
    { category: "math", "front": "6 x 10", "back": "60" },
    { category: "math", "front": "6 x 11", "back": "66" },
    { category: "math", "front": "6 x 12", "back": "72" },

    { category: "math", "front": "7 x 1", "back": "7" },
    { category: "math", "front": "7 x 2", "back": "14" },
    { category: "math", "front": "7 x 3", "back": "21" },
    { category: "math", "front": "7 x 4", "back": "28" },
    { category: "math", "front": "7 x 5", "back": "35" },
    { category: "math", "front": "7 x 6", "back": "42" },
    { category: "math", "front": "7 x 7", "back": "49" },
    { category: "math", "front": "7 x 8", "back": "56" },
    { category: "math", "front": "7 x 9", "back": "63" },
    { category: "math", "front": "7 x 10", "back": "70" },
    { category: "math", "front": "7 x 11", "back": "77" },
    { category: "math", "front": "7 x 12", "back": "84" },

    { category: "math", "front": "8 x 1", "back": "8" },
    { category: "math", "front": "8 x 2", "back": "16" },
    { category: "math", "front": "8 x 3", "back": "24" },
    { category: "math", "front": "8 x 4", "back": "32" },
    { category: "math", "front": "8 x 5", "back": "40" },
    { category: "math", "front": "8 x 6", "back": "48" },
    { category: "math", "front": "8 x 7", "back": "56" },
    { category: "math", "front": "8 x 8", "back": "64" },
    { category: "math", "front": "8 x 9", "back": "72" },
    { category: "math", "front": "8 x 10", "back": "80" },
    { category: "math", "front": "8 x 11", "back": "88" },
    { category: "math", "front": "8 x 12", "back": "96" },

    { category: "math", "front": "9 x 1", "back": "9" },
    { category: "math", "front": "9 x 2", "back": "18" },
    { category: "math", "front": "9 x 3", "back": "27" },
    { category: "math", "front": "9 x 4", "back": "36" },
    { category: "math", "front": "9 x 5", "back": "45" },
    { category: "math", "front": "9 x 6", "back": "54" },
    { category: "math", "front": "9 x 7", "back": "63" },
    { category: "math", "front": "9 x 8", "back": "72" },
    { category: "math", "front": "9 x 9", "back": "81" },
    { category: "math", "front": "9 x 10", "back": "90" },
    { category: "math", "front": "9 x 11", "back": "99" },
    { category: "math", "front": "9 x 12", "back": "108" },

    { category: "math", "front": "10 x 1", "back": "10" },
    { category: "math", "front": "10 x 2", "back": "20" },
    { category: "math", "front": "10 x 3", "back": "30" },
    { category: "math", "front": "10 x 4", "back": "40" },
    { category: "math", "front": "10 x 5", "back": "50" },
    { category: "math", "front": "10 x 6", "back": "60" },
    { category: "math", "front": "10 x 7", "back": "70" },
    { category: "math", "front": "10 x 8", "back": "80" },
    { category: "math", "front": "10 x 9", "back": "90" },
    { category: "math", "front": "10 x 10", "back": "100" },
    { category: "math", "front": "10 x 11", "back": "110" },
    { category: "math", "front": "10 x 12", "back": "120" },

    { category: "math", "front": "11 x 1", "back": "11" },
    { category: "math", "front": "11 x 2", "back": "22" },
    { category: "math", "front": "11 x 3", "back": "33" },
    { category: "math", "front": "11 x 4", "back": "44" },
    { category: "math", "front": "11 x 5", "back": "55" },
    { category: "math", "front": "11 x 6", "back": "66" },
    { category: "math", "front": "11 x 7", "back": "77" },
    { category: "math", "front": "11 x 8", "back": "88" },
    { category: "math", "front": "11 x 9", "back": "99" },
    { category: "math", "front": "11 x 10", "back": "110" },
    { category: "math", "front": "11 x 11", "back": "121" },
    { category: "math", "front": "11 x 12", "back": "132" },

    { category: "math", "front": "12 x 1", "back": "12" },
    { category: "math", "front": "12 x 2", "back": "24" },
    { category: "math", "front": "12 x 3", "back": "36" },
    { category: "math", "front": "12 x 4", "back": "48" },
    { category: "math", "front": "12 x 5", "back": "60" },
    { category: "math", "front": "12 x 6", "back": "72" },
    { category: "math", "front": "12 x 7", "back": "84" },
    { category: "math", "front": "12 x 8", "back": "96" },
    { category: "math", "front": "12 x 9", "back": "108" },
    { category: "math", "front": "12 x 10", "back": "120" },
    { category: "math", "front": "12 x 11", "back": "132" },
    { category: "math", "front": "12 x 12", "back": "144" }
];